I will try and find it out for you, Sam. And that is right, I've got NiKo with me here.
我会尽量帮你问出来的，Sam。没错，现在 NiKo 就在我身边。
You made playoffs, NiKo. karrigan's safe for now?
你们已经打进季后赛了，NiKo。那 karrigan 现在算是安全过关了？
Yeah, of course he is.
那当然了。
I mean, you know, first playoffs for him this year, I think so.
我是说，这应该算是他今年第一次打进季后赛吧，我记得是这样。
I guess it's a lot better than it was before for him. No, all jokes aside,
那对他来说肯定比之前强多了。不开玩笑了，
this was a crazy game, an intense game. You had to fight so much back against The MongolZ.
这场比赛真的太疯狂了，强度也很高。你们面对 The MongolZ，真的是一路硬撑着打回来的。
Looking at that CT side and just how the calling went for you, how you were trying to work it all out as it was getting crazy,
尤其是看你们 CT 那边的指挥过程，局势越打越乱的时候，你们是怎么一点点把它理顺的，
then into overtime you seemed to hit another gear. Can you just explain it all to me?
到了加时你们又像是直接提了一个档。你能跟我完整讲讲吗？
Yeah, I mean, I'm just trying to, really, yeah, trying to recollect everything now.
对，我现在也在努力回想整场到底是怎么发展的。
But obviously we had Danny giving pretty good ideas before the map started,
不过很明显，在地图开始之前，Danny 就已经给了我不少很不错的思路，
what we can use against them and what's good, and also what we had done before.
包括哪些东西可以拿来针对他们，哪些思路是有效的，还有我们以前用过的内容。
But yeah, I felt like I was in good control. Even though we were getting a bit shut down, T side was very hard,
但总的来说，我一直觉得自己对局面还是有掌控的。虽然我们确实一度被压住了，T 方也打得很艰难，
I still stayed in the game throughout the whole map.
但我整张图都没有脱离比赛节奏。
And I know that we have one of the best CT sides on Mirage right now.
而且我知道，我们现在的 Mirage CT 侧绝对是顶级水准之一。
I think we have actually come back multiple times already now on this side, and I just feel comfortable.
我觉得我们已经不止一次靠这边完成翻盘了，所以我打起来真的很有底。
I think, you know, the kids are also insane on this map. They're getting a lot of multi-kills,
而且几个年轻人这张图也是真的猛，经常能一波接一波地打出连杀，
and it's just about putting them in a comfort zone.
关键就是把他们放进最舒服的环境里去发挥。
And we also just have a lot of things on Mirage right now.
还有就是，我们现在这张 Mirage 手里的东西确实很多。
We can go aggressive very fast, we can go aggressive late round, we are also good when we play passive,
我们可以很快提速去打，也可以拖到后段再主动做事，就算选择偏保守的打法，我们同样也能打好，
so we have a very good balance of everything, and when everyone's hitting the shots it looks like this.
所以整体平衡性非常好。而当每个人枪都开起来的时候，比赛看上去就会变成这样。
And as you said, you know, when you get to overtime and you come back, you obviously have space to breathe,
而且就像你说的那样，一旦你们把比赛拖进加时，还完成了追分，你自然就会多出一点喘息空间，
you have space to make more mistakes, and you can just kind of do a bit more riskier plays as well.
你允许自己犯错的空间会更大，也就更敢去做一些更冒险的打法。
It just felt like that. We cracked the code, and we just understood what works,
当时给我的感觉就是这样。我们像是把那道题解开了，终于搞明白什么东西是有效的，
and it was just kind of easier to take the duels, you know, in overtime,
到了加时以后，很多对枪也就显得更容易接了，
which just helped us.
这也确实帮了我们很多。
But overall, a team effort, really. It was hard, it was looking very hard.
但总的来说，这真的是全队一起拼出来的。过程非常难，当时看起来也真的很难。
You know, Inferno was tough, and then we started getting smashed on Mirage,
你也知道，Inferno 就已经很难打了，到了 Mirage 我们前面又一度被狠狠干了一波，
so really proud of how we stayed in the game and how we kept believing until the end.
所以我特别为我们能一直留在比赛里、一直相信自己直到最后而感到骄傲。
Yeah, you really believed and it paid off for that one as well.
是的，你们确实一直都相信自己，而且这份坚持最后也得到了回报。
Looking at just the route you've had here to the playoffs, some maps being close,
再看看你们这一路打进季后赛的过程，有些地图其实都打得非常接近，
obviously there's a loss in there to 9z as well.
而且中间你们也确实输给过 9z。
How much of these moments do you put down to maybe not being as comfortable and prepared as you want to be with karrigan,
这些时刻里，有多大一部分你会归因于你们和 karrigan 还没有磨合到最舒服、最充分准备好的状态，
and with how all the pieces are being used, because you haven't had as much time?
以及整支队伍的各个拼图还没被完全放到最合适的位置上，毕竟你们没有那么多时间？
Yeah, we didn't have much time, and I think it's crazy that people expect us to win this event.
对，我们确实没有多少时间。而且我觉得大家现在就期待我们拿这个比赛冠军，其实挺疯狂的。
I think one thing is to change just a regular player on the team, but when you change IGL, you change pretty much the whole system.
我觉得，换一个普通队员是一回事，但你一旦换的是 IGL，基本上就是把整套系统都换了。
You change the whole team, you know, and we work day in and day out trying to constantly adjust,
你等于是在重塑整支队伍。我们每天都在一点点调、一直在适应，
get into the Finn system that everyone feels comfortable.
尽快融进 Finn 的体系里，直到每个人都能在里面打得舒服。
So we knew it was going to be messy, you know, in the groups and against all of these teams that we have played so far.
所以我们一开始就知道，小组赛阶段肯定会打得比较乱，面对这些一路遇到的队伍也不会轻松。
They looked very strong in practice as well. We knew it was going to be hard.
他们在训练里看起来也都很强，所以我们一直都知道这会很难。
I think The MongolZ also, they always keep delivering, and obviously 9z, you know,
The MongolZ 也是这样，他们总是能把表现打出来。还有 9z，
they also beat MOUZ yesterday, so they all play very strong.
他们昨天还赢了 MOUZ，所以这些队伍都打得非常硬。
But for us it's just about kind of getting the data, learning the Finn system,
但对我们来说，现阶段更重要的还是不断收集信息、继续学习 Finn 这套体系，
how much space we can take, how much space he gives,
搞清楚我们能吃多少空间，他又会给到队员多少自由度，
the energy, you know, we're finding out how we behave in these tough moments,
还有比赛里的能量感。我们也还在摸索，在这种艰难局面下，大家各自会是什么反应，
who needs to bring up the mood, who is gonna be...
谁需要负责把气氛提起来，谁又会在这种时候承担更多东西，
You know, just a lot of different things, even though it's just one player.
这类细节其实有很多。哪怕表面上看，你们只是换了一个人而已。
It's a completely new system, so for us obviously there's no goals, I would say, for this event,
但本质上这已经是一套全新的系统了。所以对我们来说，这次赛事其实谈不上有什么宏大的目标，
but I think playoffs was kind of mandatory, yeah, the minimum, and now we achieved it.
不过我觉得，至少打进季后赛是必须做到的，这算是最低标准，而现在我们已经完成了。
And, you know, the reason we struggled before in playoffs and the reason we brought Finn is to get over that edge.
而且我们以前在季后赛阶段之所以老是差一口气，正是因为这个，所以我们才把 Finn 带进来，想跨过那道坎。
And I'm excited to get on the stage with him again after, what, eight years.
我也很期待，时隔差不多八年之后，能再次和他一起站上舞台。
He's a big showman, and looking forward, I'm gonna enjoy it.
他本来就是个很会带舞台气氛的人，我很期待，也一定会享受这个过程。
Hopefully put on a show of it as well. I'm expecting that from you guys.
也希望我们真能把场面打得很好看。我对你们还是有这个期待的。
But looking at karrigan now, you obviously worked with him in the past. What are your initial thoughts on how he's working with the team,
不过说回 karrigan，你以前就跟他合作过。那你现在对他和这支队伍的磨合，最初的感受是什么？
what he's getting out of not just you, but the other players on the team, and how this is working currently?
不只是你，包括其他队员，他现在从大家身上激发出了什么？整套东西现在运转得怎么样？
I think it's working very well. Even though the results were messy, I think we feel very comfortable in the game.
我觉得运转得其实挺好的。虽然结果看起来有点乱，但我们在比赛里其实打得是很舒服的。
As I said, he brings a different style of game, you know.
就像我前面说的，他带来的是一种完全不同的比赛风格。
None of these players played with this type of IGL ever before, in my opinion.
在我看来，这支队里没有谁以前真正跟这种类型的 IGL 搭档过。
So it's a lot of learning, and for us it's really easy to fit into his system with these players
所以需要学习的东西很多。不过以这批人的配置来说，顺风的时候想融进他的体系其实并不难，
when we are leading, when we are feeling the momentum, right?
尤其是在我们领先、在场上已经打出势头的时候。
But when we hit, you know, when today things were a bit rough, this is where, if his system needs to work,
但一旦像今天这样，场上出现了一些不顺的时刻，那才是真正考验这套体系的时候。
we need to be constantly 100 percent in the game if his system wants to work.
如果他的体系要运转起来，我们就必须始终百分之百地留在比赛里。
So I think today we showed a little bit of weakness in that part,
所以我觉得今天我们在这一点上确实还是暴露出了一些薄弱环节，
but other than that, I think the Finn system... obviously there's a big reason why we wanted him on the team.
但除此之外，我觉得 Finn 这套东西还是很有价值的。很明显，我们之所以想让他加入，背后是有充分原因的。
We believe that he will be able to take us to the next step.
我们相信，他能把这支队伍带到下一个层级。
Well, thank you very much for your insight. One final thing on this though:
好的，非常感谢你的分享。不过最后我还想再追问一点：
you did say during this interview just now that you think it's crazy people expect you to be able to win this tournament,
你刚才在采访里说，你觉得大家现在就期待你们能拿下这项赛事，其实有点疯狂，
but you might have some of that belief yourself, right?
但你自己心里，多少也还是会相信这件事吧？
You always have to believe that you can win the tournament,
你永远都必须相信，自己是有机会赢下整项赛事的，
and I understand why people think that with the players that we have.
而且考虑到我们手里的这些选手，我也理解为什么外界会这么想。
But for us, you know, we need practice. There is no Vitality and Na'Vi, but we need more time.
但对我们来说，我们还是需要训练。是的，这次场上没有 Vitality 和 Na'Vi，可我们依旧需要更多时间。
But still, it's crazy to me that people still expect us to win.
但即便如此，大家现在就期待我们夺冠，在我看来还是很夸张。
Well, let's see if it does end up getting crazier when we get to that part of the tournament.
那就看看等比赛真正打到后面的时候，事情会不会变得更疯狂吧。
NiKo, thank you very much for your time. Sam, let's get back to you.
NiKo，非常感谢你接受采访。Sam，画面交还给你。